

Dandun Adi Nugroho

iOS Developer

+62 812 9184 2481 dandun.adi@gmail.com Banjarnegara, Central Java

Profile

I resigned my job of 4 years on aircraft maintenance industry to pursue a career on software development. I invested the time and what little money I had into an online iOS academy. I give everything I have to be at the forefront of innovation through software development.

Technical Skills

Swift
Cocoa Touch Framework
MVC, MVVM Design Pattern
Core Data, Realm, SQL
Networking
HTML
CSS

Experience

Assistant Cabin Technician

2016-2020

GMF Aeroasia

Maintain and updating In-Flight Entertainment System data on aircraft.

Junior Web Developer

2015-2016

M2D Asia

Design and developing websites using PHP Native, Wordpress, Joomla and Bootstrap.

Education

Multimedia, SMKN 1 Cibinong

2012-2015

Bogor, West Java

This is my starting point for learning design and computer science. At first grade I learn graphic design and basic web development. At second grade I learn basic Cinematography. At final grade I learn 3D Animation using Blender.

Certifications

CS50x Introduction to Computer Science

CS50 Harvard University

iOS App Development Bootcamp

Dr. Angela Yu on Udemy

Belajar Fundamental Aplikasi iOS

Dicoding Indonesia

Learn and Understand Building Modern

iOS Apps

Bennett Lee on Udemy

Projects

Explore Dieng

Explore Dieng is a travel guidance apps that help you plan your vacation at amazing places on Dieng Plateau.

Tech Stack

UlKit and Storyboards MVC Design Pattern Firebase Authentication Firebase Firestore Firebase Storage MapKit CocoaPods KingFisher











Texas Chicken & Burgers

Texas Chicken & Burgers is your go to fast food restaurants that serves up always Fresh, Halal and Southern style and comfort food every day.

Tech Stack

UlKit Programmatically No Storyboard MVVM Design Pattern Alamofire SDWebImage Swift Package Manager











